<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cracking on Hi, I&#39;m Kyle</title>
    <link>https://jovial-yonath-8d9e17.netlify.app/categories/cracking/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cracking on Hi, I&#39;m Kyle</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 00:54:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jovial-yonath-8d9e17.netlify.app/categories/cracking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Brute Force WordPress Passwords with WPScan and Tor</title>
      <link>https://jovial-yonath-8d9e17.netlify.app/2018/05/18/brute-force-wordpress-passwords-with-wpscan-and-tor/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 00:54:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jovial-yonath-8d9e17.netlify.app/2018/05/18/brute-force-wordpress-passwords-with-wpscan-and-tor/</guid>
      <description>Visit [Center City Security](https://centercitysecurity.com?utm_source=TechnicalAgain.com&amp;amp;utm_medium=https://technicalagain.com/2018/05/18/brute-force-wordpress-passwords-with-wpscan-and-tor/&amp;amp;utm_campaign=Technical Again Brute Force Wordpress Passwords with wpscan and tor&amp;amp;utm_content=header) for WordPress Penetration Testing and Security services.
I took another crack, pun intended, at brute forcing my WordPress password using WPScan. Unlike when I tried it the other day, this time I used Tor and set up a SOCKs proxy to make use of a false IP address. My thinking was that my web host might black list my IP after a certain number of failed attempts, so by using Tor I could simply switch IP addresses once the blacklist went into effect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More Password Cracking - Windows Edition with Ophcrack</title>
      <link>https://jovial-yonath-8d9e17.netlify.app/2018/04/22/more-password-cracking-windows-edition-with-ophcrack/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 21:26:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jovial-yonath-8d9e17.netlify.app/2018/04/22/more-password-cracking-windows-edition-with-ophcrack/</guid>
      <description>I continued the work I previously explained by attempting to crack a Windows administrator password. This time I created a new windows administrator, booted up using a Kali Linux USB and launched Ophcrack to go after the administrator account I set up.
After lauching Ophcrack, I navigated to the Windows partition and then \WINDOWS\System32\Config to access the SAM database. I then downloaded a Rainbow Table called Vista Free and after about 10 minutes, the admittedly weak password I setup _hello123 was cracked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Password Cracking with John the Ripper</title>
      <link>https://jovial-yonath-8d9e17.netlify.app/2018/04/17/password-cracking-with-john-the-ripper/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 02:11:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jovial-yonath-8d9e17.netlify.app/2018/04/17/password-cracking-with-john-the-ripper/</guid>
      <description>I did some preliminary experimenting with password cracking utility John the Ripper to test the security of my own root password. I started by installing John and dumping the /etc/passwd file.
sudo apt-get install john
unshadow /etc/passwd /etc/shadow &amp;gt; mypasswd.txt
The mypasswd.txt file now holds a salted hash of my root password. I then passed this over to John to work its magic.
john mypasswd.txt
John is very powerful. I experimented with the most basic of cracking settings starting with single mode, then word lists and John would have moved to an incremental mode.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>