<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>open source on Hi, I&#39;m Kyle</title>
    <link>https://jovial-yonath-8d9e17.netlify.app/tags/open-source/</link>
    <description>Recent content in open source on Hi, I&#39;m Kyle</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 02:25:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jovial-yonath-8d9e17.netlify.app/tags/open-source/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>According to Facebook, I Will Have a Dad-Bod on June 28, 2021</title>
      <link>https://jovial-yonath-8d9e17.netlify.app/2020/04/14/according-to-facebook-i-will-have-a-dad-bod-on-june-28-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 02:25:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jovial-yonath-8d9e17.netlify.app/2020/04/14/according-to-facebook-i-will-have-a-dad-bod-on-june-28-2021/</guid>
      <description>I stepped on the scale more than 1000 times in the past decade and then used Facebook&amp;rsquo;s predictive modeling framework, Prophet, to see what I will weigh in five years if I don&amp;rsquo;t make changes. At 5&amp;rsquo;9&amp;rdquo; I&amp;rsquo;ll officially have a Dad-Bod when I pass 200 lbs. on June 28, 2021.
Note: I couldn&amp;rsquo;t help myself from using a click bait headline. The only thing Facebook has to do with this post is I used an amazing open source prediction library they created called Prophet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Data Science to Pick NCAA Tournament First Round Winners</title>
      <link>https://jovial-yonath-8d9e17.netlify.app/2020/03/07/using-data-science-to-pick-ncaa-tournament-first-round-winners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 01:42:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jovial-yonath-8d9e17.netlify.app/2020/03/07/using-data-science-to-pick-ncaa-tournament-first-round-winners/</guid>
      <description>“Usually the team that scores the most points wins the game.” - John Madden
Update: If you&amp;rsquo;d like to jump right to part 2 of this series you can do so here where I turn the regression analysis into a really basic data science model.
I&amp;rsquo;m taking the first steps of an 18-24 month journey with a beginner&amp;rsquo;s mindset to establish and grow my data science skills. What better way to begin to learn new skills in March than by applying them to March Madness?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conwell Quotes - WordPress Plugin With a Backdoor</title>
      <link>https://jovial-yonath-8d9e17.netlify.app/2019/04/14/conwell-quotes-wordpress-plugin-with-a-backdoor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2019 19:41:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jovial-yonath-8d9e17.netlify.app/2019/04/14/conwell-quotes-wordpress-plugin-with-a-backdoor/</guid>
      <description>Conwell Quotes is a malicious WordPress plugin that hides a reverse shell in a backdoor behind legitimate plugin functionality. This is used for offensive security purposes.
Here is a direct download of version 1.0 of the plugin that you can add to WordPress.
You can find the open source code on GitHub.
Modeled after the Hello Dolly plugin which comes packaged on all new WordPress installation, Conwell Quotes displays a random quote on each page of the WordPress admin portal based on Conwell&amp;rsquo;s Acres of Diamonds (which is one of my favorite books).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>