<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PHP on Hi, I&#39;m Kyle</title>
    <link>https://jovial-yonath-8d9e17.netlify.app/tags/php/</link>
    <description>Recent content in PHP on Hi, I&#39;m Kyle</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2019 19:41:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jovial-yonath-8d9e17.netlify.app/tags/php/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Conwell Quotes - WordPress Plugin With a Backdoor</title>
      <link>https://jovial-yonath-8d9e17.netlify.app/2019/04/14/conwell-quotes-wordpress-plugin-with-a-backdoor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2019 19:41:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jovial-yonath-8d9e17.netlify.app/2019/04/14/conwell-quotes-wordpress-plugin-with-a-backdoor/</guid>
      <description>Conwell Quotes is a malicious WordPress plugin that hides a reverse shell in a backdoor behind legitimate plugin functionality. This is used for offensive security purposes.
Here is a direct download of version 1.0 of the plugin that you can add to WordPress.
You can find the open source code on GitHub.
Modeled after the Hello Dolly plugin which comes packaged on all new WordPress installation, Conwell Quotes displays a random quote on each page of the WordPress admin portal based on Conwell&amp;rsquo;s Acres of Diamonds (which is one of my favorite books).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maintaining Presence and Installing Backdoors</title>
      <link>https://jovial-yonath-8d9e17.netlify.app/2019/02/26/maintaining-presence-and-installing-backdoors/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 20:26:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jovial-yonath-8d9e17.netlify.app/2019/02/26/maintaining-presence-and-installing-backdoors/</guid>
      <description>By completing this exercise I learned that the best backdoor is one that you don&amp;rsquo;t need to install yourself! There are two backdoors that I opened up within the Metasploitable 2 operating system (msf2).
The most powerful and easiest backdoor was to login using the root shell, create a new superuser, and then add this user into the SSH list so that I could make use of the existing SSH server configuration.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>