<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>netcat on Hi, I&#39;m Kyle</title>
    <link>https://jovial-yonath-8d9e17.netlify.app/tags/netcat/</link>
    <description>Recent content in netcat on Hi, I&#39;m Kyle</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2019 19:41:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jovial-yonath-8d9e17.netlify.app/tags/netcat/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Conwell Quotes - WordPress Plugin With a Backdoor</title>
      <link>https://jovial-yonath-8d9e17.netlify.app/2019/04/14/conwell-quotes-wordpress-plugin-with-a-backdoor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2019 19:41:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jovial-yonath-8d9e17.netlify.app/2019/04/14/conwell-quotes-wordpress-plugin-with-a-backdoor/</guid>
      <description>Conwell Quotes is a malicious WordPress plugin that hides a reverse shell in a backdoor behind legitimate plugin functionality. This is used for offensive security purposes.
Here is a direct download of version 1.0 of the plugin that you can add to WordPress.
You can find the open source code on GitHub.
Modeled after the Hello Dolly plugin which comes packaged on all new WordPress installation, Conwell Quotes displays a random quote on each page of the WordPress admin portal based on Conwell&amp;rsquo;s Acres of Diamonds (which is one of my favorite books).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exfiltrating Data from MySQL and Postgres</title>
      <link>https://jovial-yonath-8d9e17.netlify.app/2019/02/26/exfiltrating-data-from-mysql-and-postgres/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 02:58:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jovial-yonath-8d9e17.netlify.app/2019/02/26/exfiltrating-data-from-mysql-and-postgres/</guid>
      <description>I continued experimenting with Metasploitable 2. Over the past few days I managed to gain access to the MySQL and Postgres databases and used net cat to dump the databases and export them.
Using a similar technique as before, I used a reverse shell exploit to control the host, I launched mysql, queried the database to view the users, and found that two users didn&amp;rsquo;t have passwords.
I then used the guest account to dump the tables into a zip file and used net cat to send the file from the host over to my attacker.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>